Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5825
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- USPS, 1986-87. (Box 9)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1972-1986 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Windham Community Memorial Hospital Federation of Nurses, Local 5063, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Westbury Music Fair/ Local 892 AFM, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - R.F. Zapora Motor Transportation Teamsters Union, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Westinghouse-KYW-TV IATSE, Local 804, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - WGBH/NABET, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - WGBH/NABET, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - WGBH/NABET, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Winchester School Board, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Winchester School Board, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Winchester School Board, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43)